

CA. Narahari Adhikari

Tarkeshwor -8, Balaju, Kathmandu +977-98011-45270

narahariadhikari@gmail.com

Career Summary

Young and energetic Chartered Accountant having more than seven years of career experience including more than four years of post-qualification experience in the field of Accounting, Auditing, Internal Control, Taxation, VAT, Business Planning and Project Planning. Member of 'The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (ICAI)' and 'The Institute of Chartered Accountants of Nepal (ICAN)'. Commerce Graduate (Financial Management) from Tribhuvan University, Nepal.

Career Experience

Tiger Palace Resort & Casino. [August 2017 to Present] Company Profile:

Tiger Palace Resort (*Tiger One Pvt. Ltd.*) is the Five Star Resort located in Bhairahawa, Rupandehi. Owned by Australian Company Silver Heritage Group, The Company has invested more than Rs. 5 Billion and has provided employment to more than one thousand employees in Nepal.

Position Handled: Budgeting and Planning Manager (Consultant)

Responsibilities:

- Drafted Company Financial and Procurement Policy.
- Successfully handled and completed pre-operation period.
- Successfully implemented ERP System (IDS).
- Monitoring regular accounting records
- Preparing and analyzing monthly cash flow reports
- Preparing and reporting monthly financial report to Group CFO
- Menu costing for Events, Functions and Restaurants
- Payroll management
- Inventory management
- Liaising with Central Bank, Banks and Tax (Income Tax, VAT, Excise) Authorities

BNR Business Consultancy Pvt. Ltd. [October 2015 to August 2017]

Company Profile:

BNR Business Consultancy Pvt. Ltd. is a consulting firm lead by team of Chartered Accountants in order to provide sound professional services to wide range of clients in the areas of Internal Audit, Accounting, Tax Advisory, Business/Project Planning, Management advisory and other related services.



Position Handled: Manager **Responsibilities Handled:**

- Managed overall assignments of the company
- Trained the staffs and task team to organize and conduct Internal Audit, Tax Audit, Financial Accounting and company registration services.

Vianet Communications Pvt. Ltd. [December, 2013-September, 2015]

Company Profile:

Vianet Communications Pvt. Ltd. is one of the leading Internet Service Provider (ISP) and pioneer in establishing FTTH Connection in Nepal. The Company has been providing wide range of internet service in Kathmandu valley and Pokhara since last 16 years with an efficient team of executives. The company is serving wide range of clients including NGOs, INGOs, Banks & Financial Institutions, Government sectors and private sectors.

Position Handled: Sr. Officer- Accounts & Finance (Reporting to Director Finance & Operation)

Responsibilities Handled:

- Managed the accounts and finance department
- Managed the funds of the company
- Payroll Management
- Conducted the statutory audits
- Liaising with VAT & Income tax authorities in related matters
- Dealing with Banks for Loan, LC and TT Related Transactions
- Established the inventory management system

M/s V. K Dhingra & Co., Chartered Accountants [2010-2013] Company Profile:

V. K Dhingra & Co., a Delhi based firm, was one of the top 20 Chartered Accountant firm in India in 2010. The Company has been providing wide range of consultancy services relating to audit, taxation and corporate law since long time. The Company had/has wide range of clients in India including the organizations included in list of navaratna.

Position Handled: Articled Trainee (Reporting to Partner)

Responsibilities Handled:

- Conducted Statutory Audits, Internal Audits and Tax Audits under Indian laws then in force for wide range
 of clients including Pvt. Companies, Public Companies, Individual Firms and Individual tax payers.
- Prepared financial policies and SOPs for finance department of various companies.
- Prepared budget, business forecast and financial statements for various companies.

Academic Qualifications

- Bachelor of Business Studies (BBS) in Financial Management, from Tribhuvan University (TU), Nepal in 2009 (Campus Topper-BBS, Public Youth Campus, Kathmandu) [67.86%]
- "10+2" –Management, from HSEB, Nepal in 2005 [67.20%]
- School Leaving Certificate Examination from Nepal Board in 2003 (District Second, Nuwakot) [72.37%]



Professional Qualifications

- Associate Member, ICAN
- CA Final from The ICAI in May 2013, (First attempt) [55.75%]
- CA- IPCC from The ICAI in November 2010, (First attempt) [65.71%]
- CA- CPT from The ICAI in June 2009, (First attempt) [90.5%]

Additional Trainings

- Attended in various seminars conducted by ICAN and ACAN
- 110 Hours of Information Technology Training conducted by The ICAI
- 35 Hours of Orientation Programme conducted by The ICAI
- 15 Days of General Management & Communication Skills training conducted by The ICAI

Computer Proficiency

- Well versed with Microsoft Office.
- Experienced in operating Tally, Swastik, Navigator (Accounting Software)
- Currently working with IDS Software (ERP)

Personal Details

Date of birth : 11 January 1988Father's Name : Basu Dev Adhikari

Nationality : NepaliReligion : Hindu

Permanent Address : Shivapuri-5, Nuwakot-Nepal
 Languages known : Nepali, English and Hindi

Hobbies : listening music